Manoj Kumar

Full Stack Web Developer



CONTACT



Phone

+61 40101010



Email

hello@emanoj.com



Address

75 Sample Avenue Oak Ridge, NSW 2578

EDUCATION

University of Sydney

February 2022- November 2022

Project Management (non-award)

UNSW

JUNE 2008 - DEC 2014 Entrepreneurship and Business Skills study (non-award)

Macquarie University

JUNE 2008 - DEC 2014 Bachelor of Science

HOBBIES

Videography, Walking Music Driving

ABOUT ME

My name is Manoj Kumar, based in Sydney, Australia. I've been working in business management for the last 25 years - a comprehensive journey across business management, international commerce, operational excellence, and digital advertising operations.

EXPERIENCE

Fox Co

Operational Excellence Manager July 2022 - current In this position, I work on areas related to business process, continuous improvement, innovation and compliance. The overall aim of the business unit is to improve the efficiency and efficacy of the company's operations across all the departments.

Media Ltd

Digital Advertising Lead July 2021 - July 2022

In this position, I work on areas related to business process, continuous improvement, innovation and compliance. The overall aim of the business unit is to improve the efficiency and efficacy of the company's operations across all the departments.

Real News Corp

Advertising Manager July 2017 - July 2021

In this role, I managed the Ad Operations team (recruitment, training & mentoring + escalation point for day-to-day issues), established better processes and involved in various projects across the wider Operations team.

TECH STACK

- HTML
- CSS
- Java Script
- Python